ZERADAM **FANTAYE**

San Francisco, CA **↑** (408) 509 - 3646 **↓**

zeradam.fantaye@gmail.com

LinkedIn profile in

http://zeradamfantaye.com/



PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Creative and highly motivated web developer with technical skills in end-to-end software development and web application design. Possess knowledge of various software languages and tools with fierce passion about user experience and integrate software per requirement. Experienced in object-oriented programming; developing, testing and debugging code; designing interfaces; and administering systems and networks.



EDUCATION

Computer Engineering, BS | University of California, San Diego 09/2013 – 12/2016



EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer, Intern | Smuggr, Inc 06/2015 – 09/2015

00/2013 - 09/2013

- Developed prototypes and high-quality mock-ups
- Converted Photoshop layouts to web pages using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Developed and implemented effective solutions that are integrated to company's information technology standards
- Created and implemented a custom CSS grid system, with CSS media queries for mobile responsiveness.
- Created and maintained the front-end standards document and oversaw production of JavaScript, HTML, and CSS (and PHP for the WordPress blog)
- Programmed HTML5 canvases to animate particles on web backgrounds for site-wide promotions
- Developed fully functional responsive prototypes based on Business Requirements using HTML/HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and jQuery.
- Executed and contributed to full-stack web development projects, with an emphasis on front end features, browser manipulation, and cross-browser compatibility.



TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Front-End Development: HTML5, CSS, CSS3, jQuery, Ajax, JavaScript, bootstrap, Semantic UI, UIKit
- Back-End Development: PHP, NodeJS, Express, mongoose, MongoDB, SQL server
- **High-Level Language:** C, C++, Java
- Version Control: Git, Github
- Operating Systems: UNIX, Windows, iOS
- Design Patter: MVC, RESTful API